<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Bruno Montezano</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Bruno Montezano</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to generate a normal distribution with R</title>
      <link>/post/2022/09/22/how-to-generate-a-normal-distribution-with-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2022/09/22/how-to-generate-a-normal-distribution-with-r/</guid>
      <description>What is a normal distribution? When studying statistics, we often hear a term called normal distribution. But what is it?
It is a type of continuous probability distribution for a random variable.
It is important to represent real-valued random variables in many contexts, including biostatistics and health sciences, because we often can&amp;rsquo;t know the true distribution from what these characteristics come from. And we should be able to further understand the importance of this concept when we study the central limit theorem, stating that under some conditions, the average of many observations of a random variable with finite mean and variance is also a random variable, converging into a normal distribution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>My name is Bruno Montezano. I&amp;rsquo;m pursuing my MSc in Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences at the Federal University of Rio Grande do Sul (UFRGS).
There&amp;rsquo;s more info about me on the homepage and my curriculum.
Contact You can contact on GitHub (I code almost daily). You can subscribe to the RSS feed of the blog posts.
You can also find me on LinkedIn, ResearchGate.
About this website This site is created with blogdown (base on Hugo) and the theme is hugo-xmin, a Hugo theme ported by Yihui.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cv/</guid>
      <description>Bruno Braga Montezano CV in PDF You can access it here.
Contact Information and Social Media Email: bmontezano@hcpa.edu.br
Homepage: https://bmontezano.netlify.app
GitHub: @brunomontezano
LinkedIn: @bmontezano
ResearchGate: @Bruno-Braga-Montezano
ORCID: 0000-0002-4627-1776
Publons: Bruno Braga Montezano
Google Scholar: Bruno Braga Montezano
Lattes Curriculum: 5680118320056968
Bio Currently, I am pursuing a Master&amp;rsquo;s degree at the Federal University of Rio Grande do Sul in the Postgraduate Program in Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences (CAPES 7 concept) as a Master&amp;rsquo;s Scholar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
